arpatech.com 2011-04-26

# Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect

We collect information from you when you register to our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering to our site, as appropriate, your may be asked to enter your name, or email address. You may however visit our site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to any open vacancies within Arpatech. In addition to receiving occasional company news, events, updates, related product or service information etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or any other site feature.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

No, we dont use cookies.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operation our website, conducting our business or serving you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have seperate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you agree to our privacy policy

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified by 11th September 2010.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can contact us using the information below:

Plot 20-E, 24th Commercial Street, Phase II Ext  
DHA, Karachi  
Email: [info@arpatech.com](mailto:info@arpatech.com)
